Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Business Week, 1970; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
    Notes: 1970 May 16
  - Item 8: Death of a crusader, 1970; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: James A. Wechsler, about Walter Reuther, 1970; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: John Herling's Labor Letter, 1970; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: May Wolf Reuther, Walter Philip Reuther, 1970; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
    Notes: Funeral flyer
  - Item 12: Mourners visit bier of Reuther, 1970; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Reuther killed in plane crash, 1970; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Reuther leaves hard gap to fill for labor, 1970; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Reuther, Head of UAW, killed in plane wreckage, 1970; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Reuther, Wife, 4 others die in crash of small jet, 1970; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: Reuther's legacy for social security, 1970; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: UAW Solidarity, 1970; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.13:no.6(1970:June). Copy 2
  - Item 19: Statement of Walter P. Reutherbefore the Subcommittee on Antitrust and MonopolyDecember 18, 1961, Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: Submission of Walterto repeal of Section 14(b) of the National Labor Relations Act, 1965; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 21: The nation mourns Reuther, 1970; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 22: Walter P. Reuther on First things first, 1964; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
    Notes: An occasional paper on the Free Society, published by the Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions. 2 copies
  - Item 23: Walter Philip Reuther 1907-1970, Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
    Notes: UAW Washington Report, May 18, 1970
  - Item 24: Walter Reuther, 1970; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 25: Walter Reuther: Union Pioneer with Broad influence..., 1970; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 26: Walter Reuther's great big union, 1963; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 27: articles in "Daily News" (vol.51, no.274), 1970; Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 28: Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Item 29: Western Union telegram from Victor Reuther, Publication (Box 105, Folder 7)
    Author: Victor Reuther
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Statement prepared.for Presentation to the Senate Select Committee on Improper Activities in the Labor and Management Field, 1954; Publication (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Duties of local union financial officers, 1947; Publication (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Will the UAW-CIO: retreat?, stand still?, go forward?, 1946; Publication (Box 106, Folder 1)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Labor's stake in employment and retirement, 1949; Publication (Box 106, Folder 2)
    Notes: Transcript. 2 copies
  - Item 2: Paper before joint session of American Economic Association and Industrial Relations Research Association, 1949; Publication (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: UAW-CIO collective bargaining handbook for workers security programs., 1949; Publication (Box 106, Folder 2)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Social Security Dept.
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Skilled Trades Dept. UAW, Newsletter, 1964-1965 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.1:no.2,4
  - Item 2: International Union UAW job descriptions of the skilled trades. Formulated by International Union UAW Job Description Committee., 1956; Publication (Box 106, Folder 3)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: UAW-CIO collective bargaining handbook for workers security programs., 1949; Publication (Box 106, Folder 4)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Medical Care and Rehabilitation under workman's compensation, present status and critique, 1954; Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    Notes: Thesis.
  - Item 2: The Ford-UAW-CIO workers security program plans, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Toledo industries - UAW-CIO, 1950; Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Toledo.
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Retirement - a labor viewpoint, 1951; Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Check sheet for workers security program, Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Discussion outline of majority and minority reports, 1951; Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
    Notes: Transcript
  - Item 4: Labor's approach to the retirement program, 1949; Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
    Notes: Transcript of speech. Copy 2
  - Item 5: Labor's stake in employment and retirement, 1949; Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Organized labor and social security, 1950; Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Outline of UAW-CIO Collective Bargaining for Supplementary Security Programs, March, 1949, Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
    Notes: Transcript of speech. 2 copies
  - Item 8: The hospital service labor wants - a formula for progress, 1949; Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: The responsibility for medical and hospital care - state or individual, 1950; Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: The UAW-CIO and the problem of medical care, 1950; Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Thirty-seventh annual convention of the International,October 4, 1951; Labor looks at Workmen's compensation, Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
    Notes: Address. 2 copies
  - Item 12: UAW-CIO Public Relations Dept.; re: Formation of a UAW-CIO Health and Medical Care Advisory Committee, 1948; Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: UAW-CIO Randall Company Workers Security Program, 1950; Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Unions move into supplementary security programs under collective bargaining, 1949; Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Confidential memo, 1950; Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Correspondence - "Important Announcement-the UAW-CIO Social Security Insurance Program", 1946; Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Correspondence - Fee Grievance Committee, 1950; Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: Correspondence - Staff assignments, 1950; Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Paper before annual meeting of Industrial Relations Research Association, 1952; Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Statement made by Leonard Lesser, Benefit Adequacy, 1953; Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Statement made by Leonard Lesser, The Guaranteed Annual Wage and Its Relation to the Unemployment Compensation Program, 1952; Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The crisis in work injury compensation on an doff the railroads by Jerome Pollack (reprinted from the symposium on The Federal Employers' Liability Act, 1953; Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Thirty-ninth Annual Convention of the International Assoc. of Industrial Accident Boards and Commissions, Coronado, Calif.address by Jerome Pollack, 1953; Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: p.8 & 9 of United Automobile Worker from February, 1952 - articles about health care coverage, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A labor view of health security, 1954; Publication (Box 107, Folder 2)
    Author: Jerome Pollack
    Notes: Transcript presented at the 24th annual tri-state Hospital Assembly
  - Item 2: A labor view of health security presented before the 24th Annual Tri-State Hospital Assembly, 1954; Publication (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Experience under social insurance programs for permanent and temporary disability in the United States, 1955; Publication (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Medical Care and Rehabilitation under Workmen's Compensation, 1955; Publication (Box 107, Folder 2)
    Notes: Reprinted from American Journal of Public Health, vol.45, no.5, May 1955
  - Item 5: Medical care and rehabilitation under workman's compensation, present status and critique, 1954; Publication (Box 107, Folder 2)
    Notes: Presented before the Medical Care and Industrial Hygiene Sections of the American Public Health Assoc., October 13, 1954
  - Item 6: Pension Programming from a labor viewpoint, 1954; Publication (Box 107, Folder 2)
    Notes: Reprint from the Journal of the American Society of Chartered Life Underwriters, Sprint 1954, vol.VIII, no.2
  - Item 7: UAW-CIO Retirement and Health Security Program, 1954; Publication (Box 107, Folder 2)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Absence from work due to non-occupational illness and injury what is labor doing about it?, 1956; Publication (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Experience under social insurance programs for permanent and temporary disability in the United States, 1955; Publication (Box 107, Folder 3)
    Notes: Transcript. Copy 2
  - Item 3: Financing medical care in the long pull - Jerome Pollack, 1956; Publication (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Labor and management responsibility for safety, rehabilitation and injury compensation, 1956; Publication (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Major Medical expense insurance: an evaluation, 1956; Publication (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Medical care for industrial workers: a labor viewpoint, 1956; Publication (Box 107, Folder 3)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Community concern and coordination for rehabilitation, 1957; Publication (Box 107, Folder 4)
    Notes: Keynote address
  - Item 2: Employment of the handicapped, 1959; Publication (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Health care prepayment problems of a large labor union, 1958; Publication (Box 107, Folder 4)
    Author: James Brindle
  - Item 4: Health insurance today and tomorrow: a labor view, 1958; Publication (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: The American consumer views insurance, labor view of insurance, 1957; Publication (Box 107, Folder 4)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labor's role in the more effective control of disability, 1959; Publication (Box 107, Folder 5)
    Notes: Reprinted from Compensation Medicine, vol.11, no.2
  - Item 2: The union health movement as voluntarism, 1961; Publication (Box 107, Folder 5)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Social Security Reporter, 1956; Publication (Box 107, Folder 6)
    Notes: Aug. 1956
  - Item 2: Social Security Reporter, 1958; Publication (Box 107, Folder 6)
    Notes: Oct. 1958
  - Item 3: Social Security Reporter, 1955; Publication (Box 107, Folder 6)
    Notes: Aug., Nov. 1955
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Solidar Report, 1964-1966 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1-8 (1964-1966)
  - Item 2: Solidar Report, 1966-1967 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.2:no.1-3 (1966-1967)
  - Item 3: Solidar Report, 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.3:no.4-6 (1967-1968)
  - Item 4: Solidar Report, 1968; Publication (Box 107, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.4:no.1 (1968)
  - Item 5: Solidar Report, 1968-1973 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    Notes: misc issues (1968-1973)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Strike assistance program, 1958; Publication (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: UAW strike assistance program, 1967; Publication (Box 107, Folder 8)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Pad of 'Roll Call' sheets, 1955; Publication (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: poster of the United States with some regions numbered and colored in, Publication (Box 107, Folder 9)
    Notes: Poster, no description
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Automation and technological progress, 1963; Publication (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Q's and A's about White Collar Unionism, Publication (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Resolutions and panel reports drawn up by UAW technical, office and professional conference, 1967; Publication (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Special report - White collar employees, automation and the UAW, 1963; Publication (Box 107, Folder 10)
    Author: Douglas Fraser
  - Item 5: Technical, Office and Professional Units and Locals under UAW agreements, 1964; Publication (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: UAW White Collar News from the East, Publication (Box 107, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.10:no.2
  - Item 7: Correspondence - to TOP staff, 1965; Publication (Box 107, Folder 10)
    Author: Elliot Glicksman
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Technical, Office, Professional Reporter, 1963; Publication (Box 107, Folder 11)
    Notes: vol.1:no.4-6 (1963)
  - Item 2: Technical, Office, Professional Reporter, 1964; Publication (Box 107, Folder 11)
    Notes: vol.2:no.1-9 (1964)
  - Item 3: Technical, Office, Professional Reporter, 1965; Publication (Box 107, Folder 11)
    Notes: vol.3:no.1-9 (1965)
  - Item 4: Technical, Office, Professional Reporter, 1966; Publication (Box 107, Folder 11)
    Notes: vol.4:no.1-6 (1966)
  - Item 5: Technical, Office, Professional Reporter, 1967; Publication (Box 107, Folder 11)
    Notes: vol.5:no.1-6 (1967)
  - Item 6: Technical, Office, Professional Reporter, 1968; Publication (Box 107, Folder 11)
    Notes: vol.6:no.1-5 (1968)
  - Item 7: Technical, Office, Professional Reporter, 1969; Publication (Box 107, Folder 11)
    Notes: vol.7:no.1-2 (1969)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The UAW-CIO looks at time study, 1947; Publication (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: UAW-CIO Union Counselor, 1944; Publication (Box 108, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.1 April 1944
  - Item 3: Proceedings: National UAW-CIO war veterans conference, Statler hotel, Washington, D.C., April 6 and 7, 1944., Publication (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The facts. Victory through equality of sacrifice; a program for the nation, 1942; Publication (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Triple victory program, 1942; Publication (Box 108, Folder 1)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. War Policy Division.
  - Item 6: Union counseling: out of plant services for workers-a practical program for the local unions, Publication (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: W P A must be maintained for victory and post-war period., 1942; Publication (Box 108, Folder 1)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. War Policy Committee.
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: UAW-General Motors Local Leadership, Newsletter, 1964; Publication (Box 108, Folder 2)
    Notes: June-July (1964) issues
  - Item 2: UAW Ammunition, 1954; Publication (Box 108, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1954 May
  - Item 3: UAW Ammunition, 1955; Publication (Box 108, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1955 Jan.
  - Item 4: UAW Ammunition, 1956; Publication (Box 108, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1956 Jan., June
  - Item 5: UAW Ammunition, 1957; Publication (Box 108, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1957 Mar. ,May
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: UAW Administrative Letter, 1964-1967 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.16-19 (1964-1967)
  - Item 2: UAW Ammunition, 1955; Publication (Box 108, Folder 3)
    Notes: 1955 Mar., June, Sept.-Dec.
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Proceedings, National UAW-CIO Veterans Conference, Statler Hotel, Washington, D.C., Oct. 7&8, 1952, Publication (Box 108, Folder 4)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Veterans Dept.
  - Item 3: UAW Administrative Letter, 1954-1964 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.6-16 (1954-1964)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: UAW-CIO Wage Stabilization Manual, Publication (Box 108, Folder 5)
    Notes: Looseleaf out of binder
  - Item 2: Shop stewards pocket manual on wage stabilization job description, Publication (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: UAW Administrative Letter, 1967-1971 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 19-23 (1967-1971)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: UAW-CIO Union Counselor, 1944; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Proceedings: National UAW-CIO war veterans conference, Statler hotel, Washington, D.C., April 6 and 7, 1944., Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: The facts. Victory through equality of sacrifice; a program for the nation, 1942; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Triple victory program, 1942; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Union counseling: out of plant services for workers-a practical program for the local unions, Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: W P A must be maintained for victory and post-war period., 1942; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 1)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: UAW Ammunition, 1954; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: UAW Ammunition, 1955; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: UAW Ammunition, 1956; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: UAW Ammunition, 1957; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 2)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: UAW Ammunition, 1955; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 3)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 108.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Proceedings, National UAW-CIO Veterans Conference, Statler Hotel, Washington, D.C., Oct. 7&8, 1952, Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 4)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: UAW-CIO Wage Stabilization Manual, Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Shop stewards pocket manual on wage stabilization job description, Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 5)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: War Worker, 1943; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.1, no.1,2,4,6
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: UAW-CIO GI-MAIL, 1945; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Memo to all UAW-CIO local unions, 1944; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Proceedings, National UAW-CIO Veterans Conference, Statler Hotel, Washington, D.C., April 6 and 7, 1944., Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 7)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. War Policy Division
  - Item 4: The army, the soldier, the civilian, 1944; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: UAW-CIO veterans' manual for use of local union veterans' committee, 1946; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 7)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Veterans' Dept.
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Industry profiteering is raising farmers' costs, 1956; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 8)
    Author: Donald Montgomery
    Notes: Speech
  - Item 2: UAW Voting record, 93rd Congress, 1974; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Talk about taxes, 1956; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: The case for a Fair Deal labor policy, 1949; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 8)
    Author: Hubert H. Humphrey
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Women in society and 50th anniversary of woman's right to vote, Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 9)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Women's Department.
  - Item 2: Women, then and now: an illustrated discussion of the role of working women in American life, 1954; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Facts about women who work, 1962; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Sketchesby Ben Burroughs, Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Suggested program outline for UAW Women's Committees or Councils, Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: The UAW Reporter, 1952; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.1:no.6-8 (1952)
  - Item 7: Women's rights resolution twenty fourth constitutional convention, 1974; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Correspondence, 1953; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 9)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Woodcock pledges UAW goals will not change, Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Women's Auxiliary News, 1955; Publication (Box 108.1, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.17:no.5 (1955)